Contact

lindalj2622@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/lindalaskowski-jones-ms-aprn-acnsbc-cen-nea-bc-faan-224518b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Emergency Nursing

Healthcare

Certifications

Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN®)

Publications

Barriers and Facilitators to Interprofessional-Interdepartmental Interventions: Unearthing Departmental Culture

Energize Your Staff Meetings

Linda Laskowski-Jones, MS, APRN, ACNS-BC, CEN, NEA-BC, FAAN

Editor-in-Chief, Nursing2020

Newark, Delaware

Summary

Linda Laskowski-Jones, MS, APRN, ACNS-BC, CEN, NEA-BC, FAWM, FAAN is the Editor-in-Chief of Nursing, the Journal of Clinical Excellence. She received her Bachelor's and Master's degrees in nursing from the University of Delaware as well as a Post-Graduate Certificate Program in Nursing Administration, and completed an Executive Fellowship with the Advisory Board Company in Washington, DC, and an executive education program at the Harvard Business School. Her professional nursing experience spans clinical practice in emergency and trauma care, education and leadership.

She is currently appointed to the Editorial Board of The International Journal of Emergency Nursing (UK), and has served on the Editorial Boards of the Journal of Emergency Nursing and the Journal of Trauma Nursing. She is a highly published author and national speaker on emergency and trauma topics. Formerly, she was the Vice President of Emergency & Trauma Services at Christiana Care Health System in Wilmington, Delaware, where she worked for more than 30 years as an educator, clinical nurse specialist, trauma coordinator, trauma program manager, director, and since 2006, Vice President.

Linda is on the Board of Directors of the Appalachian Center for Wilderness Medicine and is a Fellow of the Academy of Wilderness Medicine. She is also a current, longstanding member of the Blue Mountain Ski Patrol.

Experience

Lippincott Williams and Wilkins

Editor-In-Chief August 2009 - Present (11 years)

The Appalachian Center for Wilderness Medicine Board of Directors December 2011 - Present (8 years 8 months) Steering Committee member since 2010.

Wilderness Medical Society Member 2004 - Present (16 years)

Christiana Care Health System Vice President: Emergency and Trauma Services June 1987 - March 2019 (31 years 10 months) Wilmington, Delaware

Education

University of Delaware

MS, Cardiopulmonary Nursing - CNS Track · (1985 - 1988)

University of Delaware BSN, Nursing · (1979 - 1983)